I'll go.
Please.
Theme.
Entertaining play
Just cute.
It's cute.
I wanted it to be a dress.
Costume.
This is the most ideal one.
I see.
Like the round pasta.
And this big ribbon.
I'd be very happy if I had
I would be very happy.
I want to show the colors
I want to show it from the front.
I'm in charge
I don't mean color.
Like a peach.
If it were me...
Sweets?
I like sweets.
What do you like?
I like chocolate the best.
I like chocolate.
What's new with me lately
Potatoes
Who likes potatoes?
Who doesn't like potatoes?
I know you don't like potatoes.
But I like potatoes.
Cure potatoes.
Then I'd rather have chocolate.
I'd rather have chocolate.
Not chocolate fine.
You know, the all-you-can-eat kind.
That kind of thing.
It's like melted chocolate. Like melted chocolate.
Like this.
Like melted chocolate.
Here you go.
Nam-chan.
Nam-chan's costume is a bit...
I couldn't draw it yet.
Oh, wow...
She's so cute!
It looks like an octopus dumpling.
A little bit.
It's chocolate.
That's so cute!
It's so cute.
I'll put chocolate on it.
Thank you very much.
It comes with chocolate.
Oh, wow.
I'll have a little note on the bottom.
I won't spread it out too much.
Cure.
I'm here.
In the raw costume.
It's perfect.
I heard it's not finished yet.
It's already so cute.
Oh!
So cute.
Delicious.
This one.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's got chocolate on it.
It's so cute.
It's so cute. (sentence end) indicates emphasis, agreement, request for confirmation, etc.
yes
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your hard work.
Wow, she's cute.
I don't know about Kistel.
Yes, sir.
Magical Girl Who's to blame?
One book is Clean Apple
Clean Apple
Not at all
What do you mean, “Clean Apple”?
Shy Muscat
Chocolate-covered Shy Muscat
Chocolate-covered?
It's so cute!
I'm so happy!
I wanted this one, it's perfect.
This is super cute!
Diet
Get it
ár
a
hi
dj
Mr. Hoş
Ah!
ah
Guillem
bowl vessel
I'm flying I'm flying
I'm flying.
I don't know how you come up with that pose.
What do you think?
You've got a lot of poses.
I checked.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
You made the outfit exactly as I suggested.
I never thought I'd wear such a cute outfit.
I'm so, so, so happy!
I'm so excited!
Yes, I know.
It wasn't finished at the time of the fitting, so
I've been really looking forward to today.
I'm so happy to see that it's just as I imagined it would be.
I'm so happy that it's covered with chocolate!
It's so cute!
Yes, it's very important!
I feel like I can beam from here!
But surprisingly, I really like the way the fabric sparkles.
I really like it.
It's very rich.
The arms are cute too.
It matches my nails.
It's so cute!
The ribbons on her head are kinda cute too.
She made it full of ribbons.
About the order
Back.
Just once
Yes, glitter
Yes, sir.
I may never wear such a cute outfit.
I think it would be absolutely adorable if 13 of us wore this outfit.
I'm sure you'll all look adorable in these outfits.
Please, please, please, please!By all means.
If you want to see how cute I am
Please vote for me!
Please support me!
Yes, sir.
Yes! Yes!
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, please vote for me.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes.